

### **OBJECTIVE**

Self-motivator good at finding reliable solutions for system issues. Experienced in working as a full-stack developer and leading an offshore team. Providing reliable skills in both development and technical communication. Fluent in English&Japanese and accustomed to working with cross-cultural teams.

## **RELEVANT SKILLS**



## **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

# Accenture, Tokyo, Japan

Application Development Specialist, April 2021-Present

- Developing and maintaining pages&features for consumer-oriented web system (Maintenance, Vue2, Typescript).
- Developed abundant pages&features for business-oriented web system (New Development, Vue3, Typescript)
- Developed abundant pages&features for consumer-oriented cosmetic App on the Android&iOS platform (New Development, Flutter, Dart)
- Migrated Flutter SDK's major version from 1.X.X to 2.X.X for an internal fundamental architecture which is commonly used by multiple projects (Flutter, Dart)

## D.A.Consortium Inc., Tokyo, Japan

Full-Stack Software Engineer, April 2018-March 2021

- Created detailed specifications and developed features that satisfied clients' expectations on an Ads delivering configuration system and a reporting system.
- Trained and led an offshore team that continuously contribute to multiple projects.
- Created and maintained a CI/CD pipeline to simplify and expedite the deployment of a new start project by using CircleCI.
- Involved in the development of SDK for Ads delivery located on iOS/Android.

### Works Applications Co., Ltd., Tokyo, Japan

Software Engineer, April 2016-March 2018

- Involved in designing and developing the features of CRE web system based on Javascript and Java(MVC).
- Implemented performance improvement of continuous integration(CI).

### **EDUCATION**